[{"answer": "We are in Green Square, that the rebels are now calling Martyr Square.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Sara, where are you and what's going on?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "It depends on who you ask, Wolf.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Do they believe he may have escaped the country?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "My thoughts, I'm so grateful for this day -- the end of tyranny, the end of brutal dictatorship, the beginning of a new universe, a new horizon for Libya.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What are your thoughts?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Do you intend to go back yourself?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "I would like him really to get caught and be put on trial, because a lot of Libyans who suffered under Gadhafi -- who he has killed, maimed, brutalized.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "And what would you like to see happen to Gadhafi?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "It's the beginning.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Has this been the best day of your life?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, it's really nice to be with you.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "What has been your view from the White House?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "We're hearing all sorts of rumors but we try not to focus on rumors on here but rather on facts.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Or how they may be getting him away?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "We've been very gratified to hear the very sound statements from the TNC's leadership, that is to say the opposition group's leadership, including as early as today from one of their ministers, Jibril is his name, gave a very good set of comments about the kind of inclusive government they see going forward.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "How confident is the White House in the rebels and in the future plan for Libya without Gadhafi?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, I think what we've seen, obviously, is that his ruthless ways did not bring stability, but a great deal of instability.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "How confident are you guys that in the short to midterm, the stability of the region will be stabilized and not, in fact, further endangered by instability of him actually going after so long?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Well, the important thing here, Piers, is that we're not in a position to decide that.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Or would his death be a preferred option?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, I think he -- we talked about this yesterday.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What is the end game for Gadhafi personally?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, what the family wanted was some type of exit strategy and they didn't have that.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "What is your view and assessment of what exactly may be happening now?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I think a lot of it is.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Is this all just bluff, do you think?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, the leadership of the NTC, of course, are primarily former Gadhafi loyalists.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Because of that, can we have more confidence that the NTC will do a good job here?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Were you always confident that this day would come?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I think what we said from the beginning, there was an act in that room that was consensual, not forcible and I think we're going to leave it at that.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Do you -- does your client, for example, concede that he behaved inappropriately, if not in any criminal way, but just inappropriately?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, it's difficult to celebrate entirely on a day like today, when it wasn't three months ago when he was in Rikers Island in an orange jumpsuit.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What is your view of how the legal system people like Dominique Strauss-Kahn before they are being convicted of anything?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "I said outside court today -- and I'll repeat it again -- that unless you yourself have been accused falsely of a serious crime that you did not commit, I think it's impossible to really understand the full measure of relief that Dominique Strauss-Khan and Anne Sinclair felt today.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "But how -- how has this manifested itself on their relationship, your client and his wife?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I think the media is partially at fault in this rush to judgment that Mr. Taylor spoke about earlier.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "In particular, there were headlines in some of the daily tabloids, \"Le Perv,\" playing off his French background, and off the supposition that he was obviously guilty?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "He is certainly happy.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Mr. Taylor, how would you describe Dominique Strauss-Khan's mood today, after all of this?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I think, with respect to questions involving allegations in France, I am going to turn to my partner, Bill Taylor, who has dealt with those issues primarily.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Are you worried about any of these kind of cases now progressing against him?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I think what we don't do in the United States of America is prosecute people criminally for behavior that someone else might find to be either inappropriate or offensive.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Does he have a sense of regret personally about his actions?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I don't think he's had an opportunity to think that through.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Is he keen to get back in the fray?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, the financial cost has been enormous.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What has been the financial cost?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "It's absolutely false.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "What was your reaction to that specific claim?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I think collectively we view her as either evil or pathetic or both.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "What would your client's view of his accuser be today?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Because surely it can't not be factored in that this has collapsed today?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Careful.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "When did you first meet Jon?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Did you think you were marrying the next Freddy Mercury?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Forty year ride, 40 year motorcycles.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "You ride Harleys?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Something like that.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Because I think he's the greatest leader out there.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Why should he be president?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "The principles are the same, whether in Utah or whether on a national basis.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "What is your great master plan?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I'm not the compromise guy.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Why would you vote against that?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "The thinking there was we had a little more love to give.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "What was the thinking there?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I have a deep belief in God.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Where do you see the line drawn in terms of your adherence to the Mormon faith?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I'd say, you know, there are 13 million Mormons around the world today.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "You start out by calling me boring.", "docId": "110823pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Is that what you're getting at?", "qSentId": 561}]